fooman.co.nz 2018-12-23

# Privacy Policy

## Scope

  * This statement applies to all Fooman websites.

## Personal information

  * We collect the information you choose to provide us when ordering or registering
  * We use common internet technologies, such as cookies and beacons, on our websites and emails.
  * We use analytics and marketing services provided by a range of 3rd parties
  * For more information about our information collection practices, please click [here](https://store.fooman.co.nz/privacy-full-v2.00/).

## Uses

  * We use personal information to fulfill your order and to provide you with information you requested.
  * We do not share your personal information with third parties.
  * We will use personal information you provide only for purposes consistent with the reason you provided it.
  * When we temporarily provide personal information to companies that perform services for us, such as to send you email or deliver your order, we require those companies to protect the information in the same manner as Fooman These service companies cannot use your personal information for any other purpose than the reason you provided it to us.

## Choices

  * You may access personal information that we hold about you. You can ask us to correct any errors or delete the information we have about you.
  * You may opt-in to our newsletter and newsfeeds
  * To protect your privacy and the privacy of others, we may have to verify that you are who you say you are before we can give you access to, or change, information about you.

## How to contact us

  * E-mail or via our contact us page
  * Fooman Limited, 3638/17B Farnham Street, Parnell, Auckland 1052

To see our full privacy policy, click [here](https://store.fooman.co.nz/privacy-full-v2.00/).
